top of page

* More

Use tab to navigate through the menu items.

#### Privacy Information

Privacy Information

When using our website and during business cooperation with us, personal data is processed. The entity  
responsible for processing is Global Event Technologies GmbH &amp; Co KG, Neualmerstraße 37, 5400 Hallein, Austria  
("GET"). For questions about data protection at GET or to exercise your rights, please contact our Data Protection  
Officer at [privacy@get.systems](mailto:privacy@get.systems).

You have the right to access, rectify, and delete your data, the right to restrict processing, to object to processing  
(particularly to object to direct marketing), as well as the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

Your data will generally not be disclosed to third parties unless it is absolutely necessary for fulfilling the purpose of  
the processing or legally required. We also share data with service providers (processors) who technically support  
us in providing systems. However, these processors are not permitted to use the data for their own purposes and  
are bound by additional agreements to the strict provisions of the General Data Protection Regulation.

Data processing typically takes place within the European Union. Should data be transferred to countries outside  
the European Union in exceptional cases (e.g., for error analysis) or if a service provider does not offer processing  
within the European Union, we ensure that either an adequacy decision by the EU Commission for the respective  
country exists or the EU Standard Contractual Clauses are concluded to ensure a high level of data protection.

Data Processing on Our Website

Web Server Logs  
When you access our website, information about the access (date, time, viewed page, IP address) is stored as log  
files on our server. This is done out of legitimate interest to monitor technical operations, optimize our information  
offering, and detect attacks on our website. We evaluate these data exclusively for our own statistical purposes in  
an anonymized form. The log files are deleted after three months.

General Inquiries / Support Form  
When you contact us via email, phone, instant messenger, or online chat, your personal data will be processed for  
customer support purposes to respond to your inquiry (Art. 6 (1) b GDPR) and based on our legitimate interest (Art. 6 (1) f GDPR) to optimize the quality of our customer service and for the assertion, exercise, or defense of legal  
claims for no longer than three years. The processed data includes your email address (when using email as a  
communication channel), your phone number (when contacting us by phone), the IP address of your device (when  
using instant messenger or online chat), and the respective communication contents or data required to respond to  
the inquiry.

Support Chat (Intercom)  
In addition to contacting us via email, you can also communicate with our support team via an online chat. For this,  
we use the services of Intercom (www.intercom.com). Our partner Intercom is not permitted to use the collected  
data for their own purposes and is bound by a data processing agreement to the requirements of the General Data  
Protection Regulation. Data is only transferred to Intercom if you explicitly activate the support chat.

Intercom Inc. is committed to complying with the provisions of the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF), which has  
been recognized by the European Commission as providing adequate protection for personal data. Therefore, no  
further legal basis is required for data transfer to the USA according to Art. 45 GDPR.

For answering your questions or selecting responses from the support team, methods of artificial intelligence may  
be used. However, these are not used for automated decision-making or creating user profiles, but solely to select  
the most likely correct answer based on an extensive knowledge database.

Notice on the Use of Cookies  
This website uses software to analyze the usage of the website. By evaluating this data, valuable insights into the  
needs of users can be gained, which helps to further improve the quality of the offering.

In this context, so-called cookies are used. Cookies are data stored in your browser that enable the recognition of a  
visitor on an anonymous basis. Cookies can generally be rejected or deleted through appropriate browser settings.  
The statements made here regarding cookies also apply similarly to other technical browser functions such as Local  
Storage and Session Storage.

Some of the cookies on this website are necessary for the website's functionality and are set based on our  
legitimate interest in the secure and efficient operation of the website. Generally, information is not shared with  
third parties for their own business purposes. Some of the cookies are used by our host, Wix.com, to protect the  
website against cyberattacks and to analyze errors. Information about these cookies can be found at  
[https://support.wix.com/en/article/cookies-and-your-wix-site](https://support.wix.com/en/article/cookies-and-your-wix-site). Wix Inc., based in the USA, as the provider of  
wix.com, is certified under the EU-US Data Privacy Framework and thus guarantees a level of data protection  
comparable to that in the EU. According to Art. 45 GDPR, no additional legal basis is required for the transfer of  
data to Wix Inc.

Cookies for the purpose of analysis and profiling are used only with your explicit consent. You can withdraw your  
consent at any time by clicking at "Cookie settings" the bottom left.

Google Analytics  
For error analysis and statistical evaluations of our web offering, and only with your consent, our website uses the  
analytics service Google Analytics provided by Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4,  
Ireland, Tel: +353 1 543 1000, Fax: +353 1 686 5660, Email: support@google.com ("Google"), which in turn  
transfers your data to the USA for further processing. Please note that the USA has a lower level of data protection  
compared to the EU, and US companies are obligated to disclose data to courts, law enforcement agencies,  
supervisory authorities, or security organizations. Google has committed to complying with the principles of the EU-  
US Data Privacy Framework (DPF) to achieve a level of data protection comparable to that in the EU. Therefore,  
according to Art. 45 GDPR, no additional legal basis is required for the transfer of data to the USA.

Google also uses the collected information for its own purposes. Further information can be found at  
[https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

Click at the bottom left at "Cookie settings" to withdraw your consent for the use of Google services for future effect.

Integration of Google Services  
With your consent, our website uses the following services provided by Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House,  
Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland, Tel: +353 1 543 1000, Fax: +353 1 686 5660, Email: support-at@google.com ("Google"), which in turn transfers your data to the USA for further processing. Please note that the USA has a  
lower level of data protection compared to the EU, and US companies are obligated to disclose data to courts, law  
enforcement agencies, supervisory authorities, or security organizations. Google has committed to complying with  
the principles of the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF) to achieve a level of data protection comparable to that  
in the EU. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no additional legal basis is required for the transfer of data to the  
USA.

As part of your consent, you have the option to enable or disable individual services.

We use the following Google services:  
\- Google Analytics: For error analysis and statistical evaluations.  
\- Google Tag Manager: To integrate other Google services.  
\- Google DoubleClick: For displaying and distributing online advertisements.  
\- Google Adwords Conversion Tracking: To measure clicks and conversions.  
\- YouTube: We embed YouTube videos, which are also provided by Google.

Google also uses the collected information for its own purposes. Further information can be found at  

Click at the bottom left at "Cookie settings" to withdraw your consent for the use of Google services for future effect.

Google Consent Mode (Basic)  
When using our website, data about your consents may be shared with Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House,  
Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland ("Google"). This only occurs if you have given consent for this data transfer. Google  
uses this information to determine the purposes for which the other transmitted data may be used.

During data processing, a transfer to countries outside the European Union, particularly to the USA, may occur. The  
USA generally has a lower level of data protection compared to the EU. However, Google voluntarily commits to  
complying with the measures of the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF). The EU Commission has certified that  
participants of the DPF achieve a level of data protection comparable to the EU. Therefore, according to Art. 45  
GDPR, no additional legal basis is required for the transfer of data to Google in the USA.

Facebook Connect  
Facebook Connect is provided by Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin  
2, Ireland ("Meta").

Facebook Connect allows you to use your Facebook profile for a simplified login to our web shop, significantly  
speeding up the registration process. Of course, a Facebook account is required to use this feature. When you use  
Facebook Connect, technical telemetry data, such as your IP address, is transmitted to Meta during the login  
process, and profile data from your Facebook account is shared with us to identify you.

We integrate Facebook Connect into our website only with your consent.

Meta transfers data to the USA as part of providing its services. Please note that the USA has a lower level of data  
protection compared to the EU, and US companies are required to disclose data to courts, law enforcement  
agencies, supervisory authorities, or security organizations. However, Meta voluntarily commits to complying with  
the measures of the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF). The EU Commission has certified that participants of the  
DPF achieve a level of data protection comparable to the EU. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no additional  
legal basis is required for the transfer of data to Meta in the USA.

Facebook Pixel  
In some cases, we advertise on the social media platform Facebook, operated by Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd., 4  
Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Ireland ("Meta"). When you click on this advertising, you are  
redirected to our own website.

We only integrate the Facebook Pixel into our website with your consent.

​

With the information from Facebook Pixel, we can check which ads were more or less successful. This involves  
logging which pages of our website were viewed after clicking on the advertisement.

Meta transfers data to the USA as part of providing its services. Please note that the USA has a lower level of data  
protection compared to the EU, and US companies are obligated to disclose data to courts, law enforcement  
agencies, supervisory authorities, or security organizations. However, Meta voluntarily commits to complying with  
the measures of the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF). The EU Commission has certified that participants of the  
DPF achieve a level of data protection comparable to the EU. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no additional  
legal basis is required for the transfer of data to Meta in the USA.

For the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as  
your rights and setting options for protecting your privacy, please refer to Facebook's privacy policy:  

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to collect data about you via this online offering and link  
it to your member data stored on Facebook, you must log out of Facebook before using our online offering and  
delete your cookies. Further settings and objections to the use of data for advertising purposes can be made within  
the Facebook profile settings: [https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads). Disabling the use of data for  
advertising purposes does not stop the collection of data itself.

LinkedIn  
Our online offering includes functions and content of the LinkedIn service, provided by LinkedIn Corp., Sunnyvale,  
California, USA, and operated by LinkedIn Ireland Unlimited Company, Wilton Place, Dublin 2, Ireland. These may  
include content such as images, videos, or texts and buttons that allow users to express their liking for the content,  
follow the authors of the content, or subscribe to our posts. If users are members of the LinkedIn platform,  
LinkedIn can assign the access to the aforementioned content and functions to the profiles of the users there.

Additionally, integrating LinkedIn allows us to track the effectiveness of our marketing measures on the LinkedIn  
platform. You can find LinkedIn's privacy policy at [https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy). Data is only  
transferred to LinkedIn if you have given us your consent for this. Even without giving consent, our website can be  
used to its full extent. You can revoke your consent at any time in the privacy settings of this website.

When activating LinkedIn functions, data may also be transferred to countries outside the European Union, where a  
lower level of data protection prevails. LinkedIn voluntarily commits to complying with the measures of the EU-US  
Data Privacy Framework (DPF). The EU Commission has certified that participants of the DPF achieve a level of data  
protection comparable to the EU. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no additional legal basis is required for the  
transfer of data to Meta in the USA.

Cloudflare  
To enhance the performance of our website and detect attacks, we use the services of Cloudflare Inc., 101  
Townsend Street, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. Some website content is loaded directly from Cloudflare's servers  
by your browser, which means Cloudflare also gains knowledge of your IP address. This information is only used to  
provide IT security services. You can find Cloudflare's privacy policy at [https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy).

Cloudflare is committed to complying with the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF), recognized by the European  
Commission as providing adequate protection for personal data. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no further  
legal basis is required for the transfer of data to the USA.

Use of YouTube  
This website uses YouTube to display videos. YouTube is a service of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway,  
Mountain View, California 94043, USA. By using YouTube, information about the use of this website can be  
transferred to Google in the USA. When you access a page on our website that contains YouTube videos, your  
browser establishes a direct connection with Google's servers. The video is then transmitted directly to your  
browser and embedded into the website. We have no influence over the scope of data collected by Google in this  
manner. To the best of our knowledge, this includes at least the following data:

\- Date and time of the visit to the relevant webpage,  
\- Internet address or URL of the accessed webpage,

\- IP address,  
\- Viewed video and the quality settings used.

We have no control over the further processing and use of the data by Google and therefore cannot take  
responsibility for it. For the purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of the data by  
Google, as well as your rights and settings to protect your privacy, please refer to Google's privacy policy at  
[https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

Google LLC is committed to complying with the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF), recognized by the European  
Commission as providing adequate protection for personal data. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no further  
legal basis is required for the transfer of data to the USA.

General Information on the Processing of Personal Data of Customers, Prospective Customers, Suppliers, and Other Business Partners

In the course of the business relationship with GET, personal data of customers, prospective customers, suppliers,  
or other business partners is processed for the purposes of ordering and delivering products and services, sales  
activities, purchasing, accounting, customer support, and for sending direct advertising. This processing is based on  
existing contracts, pre-contractual measures, or on GET's legitimate interest in sending direct advertising.

The processed data includes names and contact details, any agreements, and communication or order history. The  
provision of this data is necessary for the business relationship, as contractual or statutory obligations cannot  
otherwise be fulfilled.

The data will be stored for a maximum of three years after the last contact following the expiration of the statutory  
retention periods (usually seven years).

Information on the Processing of Applicant Data  
If you apply for a position advertised by GET, the data you provide will be processed for the purpose of applicant  
selection and for creating statistical evaluations. The legal basis for this processing is Art. 6 (1) b GDPR (pre-  
contractual measures). Please note that for some positions, especially in security areas (e.g., system  
administration), additional information may be requested.

If an employment relationship is established, GET, as your employer, will retain your data for the duration of your  
employment and delete it after the end of your employment following the statutory retention periods. If no  
employment relationship is established, the data will be stored for seven months after the conclusion of the  
application process and then anonymized, so that no personal reference can be made. A longer retention period  
will only occur if you have given us separate consent.

Data will generally not be forwarded to third parties. Exceptions include forwarding to technical service providers  
(processors) who support GET in managing applicant data, but these service providers are not allowed to use the  
data for their own purposes and are bound by separate agreements to the strict provisions of the General Data  
Protection Regulation.

Special Provisions for Video Conferences and Online Meetings with Microsoft Teams  
During the conduct of online meetings or video conferences, personal data such as contact details, video, and audio  
data are processed. This processing is necessary to fulfill contractual obligations or pre-contractual measures (e.g.,  
employment contract for employees, preliminary discussions for projects) if no other, less severe means can be  
used as efficiently and is only carried out for the duration of the respective meeting.

Data on participation in the online meeting and any text entered by participants in the chat window of the meeting  
will be deleted after the statutory retention periods (generally seven years).

In exceptional cases, recordings of the online meeting may be made for documentation, quality control, or creating  
minutes. This is done either to fulfill contractual obligations or in GET's legitimate interest in the previously  
mentioned processing purposes and only after informing all present participants. You have the right to object to  
the processing if you are in a particular situation where your rights and freedoms outweigh GET's interests.  
Recordings will only be stored as long as necessary to achieve the respective processing purpose, such as creating  
and confirming minutes.

​

Data processed during online meetings is generally not disclosed without consent, unless required by law or  
contractually necessary. Exceptions include the transfer to processors who work exclusively on GET's instructions,  
do not use the data for their own purposes, and are bound by separate agreements to the data protection  
obligations of the General Data Protection Regulation, as well as the transfer of diagnostic and telemetry data  
necessary for the operation and security of the online meeting infrastructure, which may also contain personal  
data, to Microsoft Ireland Operations Ltd., One Microsoft Place, Dublin, D18 P521, Ireland. In rare cases, this also  
involves data transfers to countries outside the European Union. Microsoft has committed to complying with the  
EU-US Data Privacy Framework (DPF), recognized by the European Commission as providing adequate protection  
for personal data. Therefore, according to Art. 45 GDPR, no further legal basis is required for the transfer of data to  
the USA.

© Global Event Technologies.

bottom of page
